<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>bovo.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Bovo</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Bovo</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Bovo</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Bovo</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Bovo</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Bovo</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxBovoxx</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      Bovo is a Gomoku (from Japanese 五目並べ - lit. "five points") like game for two players, where the opponents
      alternate in placing their respective pictogram on the game board. (Also known as: Connect Five, Five in a row, X and O,
      Naughts and Crosses)
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Bovo is en Speel as Gomoku (ut japaansch 五目並べ“ - „fief Pünkt“) för twee Spelers. De Twee wesselt sik af un leggt ehr Piktogramm op't Speelbrett. (Warrt ok „Fief verbinnen“, „Fief in de Reeg“, „X un O“ oder „Nixen un Nullen“ nöömt.)</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Bovo is een Gomoku (uit het Japans 五目並べ - letterlijk "vijf punten")-achtig spel voor twee spelers, waar de opponenten afwisselen in het plaatsen van hun respectievelijke pictogram op het spelbord. (Ook bekend als: Boter-Kaas-en-Eieren, Vijf verbinden, Vijf op een rij, X en O, Naughts and Crosses)</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Bovo to gra dla dwóch graczy w rodzaju Gomoku (z japońskiego 五目並べ - lit. "pięć punktów"), gdzie gracze na zmianę umieszczają odpowiadające im piktogramy na planszy. (Gra znana również jako: Połącz piątkę, Piątka w rzędzie, X i O, Kółko i krzyżyk)</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Bovo — гра, подібна до гомоку (від японського 五目並べ — букв. «п’ять точок»), розрахована на двох гравців. У грі суперники почергово малюють власні значки на ігровій дошці. Інші назви гри: з’єднай п’ять, п’ять у рядок, хрестики-нулики.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxBovo is a Gomoku (from Japanese 五目並べ - lit. "five points") like game for two players, where the opponents alternate in placing their respective pictogram on the game board. (Also known as: Connect Five, Five in a row, X and O, Naughts and Crosses)xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://games.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=bovo</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdegames/bovo/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/bovo.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>bovo</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
